# Curriculum vitae



# PATRYCJA GOJLIK

Adress: Gzira, Malta

Phone: 0035699774039

E-mail: admin@netiadesign.eu

Nationality: Poland

Date of birth: 07/02/1989

# **EDUCATION**

> 2009 IT and programmer, graphic designer (study) - Szczecin, Poland

2009 Career guidance course, Course of running your own business, course in entrepreneurship

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

√ 03.2019 – 07.2019

# Marketing Manager for Central Comfort Apartments and Pure Cyprus Restaurant - LONDON

- Website (designing, reparing, coding, e-commerce, optymalization, hosting administration, plugins, DNS, domain migration, SEO, ordering systems)
- Google My Business (administration)
- Google ADS ( advertising )
- Google Analytics
- Facebook and other social media( paid advertising )
- Design of leaflets, banners, new menu, logo
- · Hosting administration
- E-mail marketing
- · SMS marketing

# Hotel Manager, Marketing Admin and Programmer, data base, accounting in Forest House

# **Hotel. - LONDON**

- New website design
- All office administration and customer service care
- Calculation of company incomes and losses, VAT
- Rooms pricing relative to competition
- Solving any difficult situation
- Transfers and returns, discounts
- Advertising in media
- Running a customer base
- Supervising/helping employees and much more
- ✓ 03.2017 till now

# Web Designer, Programmer and Marketing Manager in NetiaDesign LTD (www.netiadesign.eu ) - LONDON

√ 03.2017 – 05.2017

# Private Complex accounting for Self employed individuals, benefits claims - LONDON

- Registration of self-employment
- Self employed suspension
- Annual self employed accounts/ TAX return's
- Child benefit
- Working tax credit
- Housing benefit
- Employment and support allowance
- √ 05.2016 03.2017 Stansted Express ( Airport ) ( Customer Service ) LONDON
- Information for the customer
- Customer assistance
- Health and safety

- Product sales
- Settlements of sold products
- **✓** 05.2015 05.2016 **Coffee Shop Manager LONDON**
- √ 02.2013 01.2015 Waitress ( restaurant ) LONDON
- ✓ 06.2011 02.1013 Disabled person Carer LONDON
- ✓ 06.2010 09.2010 Practice in a beauty salon LONDON

# **OTHER EXPERIENCES**

- Driving Licence ( Automatic )
- Extensive experience in all kinds of Hotel programs
- Extensive experience in all kinds of IT programs
- Web Designer, Graphic Designer (ordering systems, booking systems, website payments)
- Accounting for hotel and individual self employment, experience ( UK )
- High level of Marketing and advertising experience
- Very good computer skills
- Experience in all aspects of administration
- Good telephone manner
- Responsible for entrusted tasks
- Punctual
- Good team player and variety of customer service experience
- Preparing Terms and Conditions, New Instructions Letters, Reduction Letters, Offers Letters
- Invoicing: Designing, Arranging, Printing, Ordering, Updating and monitoring

# **QUALITY**

- o An interest in accounting and finance issues
- o The ability to think analytically, synthesize and consolidate data
- o The ability to work in a team, well developed interpersonal skills
- o Prepared to take on new challenges and learn new skills

# **ABOUT ME**

#### Hello

I'm a 30 years old lady. I have been working for 9 years in London. My life motto is: If you want, you can learn everything. I'm ready to start a new role immediately.

I am literate in various hotels and letting, marketing, booking programs. I have experience as a Marketing Manager, Web designer, Hotel manager, Private accounting. I am looking for an opportunity to work with a good team, where I can use all my skills and learning something new.

The last point is my goal:)

My programing skills would let me create for you a new, appealing and useful website. (please check one from my portfolio: www.foresthouselondon.co.uk) or mobile application.

I possess marketing skills which will enable you to find more clients and provide a high level of service. The office is my home, I can deal with every aspect of office work. I will really enjoy working with clients and am able to build good working relationships with them. The goal is to – bring more clients. Please check my skills: www.netiadesign.eu.

Website created for my hotel: <a href="https://www.foresthouselondon.co.uk">www.foresthouselondon.co.uk</a> Website created for my restaurant: <a href="https://www.purecyprus.net">www.purecyprus.net</a>

Website created for my flats: www.centralcomfortapartments.com

My own website: www.netiadesign.eu

I can work for your company as a Marketing Specialist, Programmer, Accountant, Secretarial, Office Assistant, Administration, Office Manager. I'm looking forward to hearing from you in due course and will happy to meet you on the interview.

I'm looking forward to hearing from you. Yours sincerely

Patrycja Gojlik